

Tegar SetioSoftware Engineer

• EXECUTIVE SUMMARY

I am a Software Engineer specializing in Web Development. I have contributed to a wide range of projects, from large-scale initiatives to small business ventures. Currently, I work part-time as a Front-End Engineer at PT. Kreatif Indonesia, and I am also a freelancer on the fastwork platform.

• SPECIALIZATIONS

- Html
- Css
- Bootstrap
- Scss
- Tailwind Css
- JavaScript
- TypeScript
- React
- Next Js
- Express Js

EDUCATION HIGHLIGHTS

Rakamin Academy

Full Stack Web Development Intensive Bootcamp

Agustus 2023 - Desember 2023

- understand Introduction to the World of Programming
- understand and implement Hml, Css & JavaScript Fundamentals
- understand and implement Version Control
- understand and implement OOP & DOM,
 Database, Node Js & Rest Full API, Express
 Js, React Js, Next Js, Final Project
 Discussion & Final Presentation

Tel-U Purwokerto

S1 Teknik Informatika

2021 - Now

CAREER SUMMARY

Freelancer Fastwork

19 August 2023 - Now

Front end Engineer PT.Hudoro Solusi Digital

1 April 2024 - juli 2024

• Front end Engineer PT. Sineas Kreatif Indonesia

1 August 2024 - Now

LISENSI DAN SERTIFIKASI

Sololearn

- Sololearn Certified HTML course May 2022
- Sololearn Certified Css course August 2022

Dicoding

- Belajar Membuat Front-End Web untuk Pemula August 2022
- Belajar Dasar Pemrograman Web August 2022

Rakamin Academy

 Full Stack Web Development Intensive Bootcamp December 2023

Kemdikbud

 Finalis Gemastik September 2023

CONTACT ME

- in Tegar Setio
- **9** +62 882005090497
- tegarsetio02@gmail.com
- web_profile
- Bantarbolang, Kab Pemalang
- kopsus